Nehreet Kaur

1900 Simond Avenue, Apt. 4061, Austin, TX - 78723

+1-908-381-4165

kaur.nehreet@gmail.com 💟

LINKEDIN in

GitHub #

Experienced professional looking for a full-time Web Developer/Software Programmer job. I am an experienced professional with 7+ years of experience in the healthcare industry in United Kingdom (UK). I have excellent verbal and written communication skills. I take great initiative in my work and have the ability to work as part of a team. I am a motivated individual with a drive to achieve and finish the task. I am quite compassionate with growth-mindset. I am currently pursuing Bootcamp course at UT Austin in Web-Development. I am looking forward to begin my professional carrier journey as web-developer.

Skills

- Strong Software Coding fundamentals
- HTML, CSS, JavaScript, jQuery, Ajax,

• Tools: Microsoft VS Code, Git Bash

Operating System: Windows

Experience

Care Assistant

Ann Marie Howes Centre

Birmingham City Council, Birmingham, UK

April 2014- Dec 2014

Direct Care Provider

Ann Marie Howes Centre

Birmingham City Council, Birmingham, UK

September 2009 to February 2013

Care Assistant

Palmers Croft Care home

Birmingham City Council, Birmingham, UK

June 2006 to Aug 2009

Education and Certifications

2020

JS, HTML, CSS for Web / Johns Hopkins University

Certification through Coursera. Certificate ID:

2020

Programming with JS, HTML, CSS / Duke University

Certification through Coursera. Certificate ID: V7VLLZLKCH4Y

2000 - 2003

Bachelor of Internet Sciences / Kurukshetra University

LEVEL-3 PROMOTE GOOD PRACTICES IN HEALTH AND SOCIAL CARE

ISSUED- AUTHORITY CITY&GUILDS AUG 2012

CREDENTIAL ID J/601/9470

LEVEL-2 NVQ IN HEALTH AND SOCIAL CARE

ISSUED- AUTHORITY CITY&GUILDS AUG 2008

CREDENTIAL ID 100/4792/X

FIRST AID

ISSUED- AUTHORITY BIRMINGHAM CITY COUNCIL

ISSUED ON AN 2010 EXPIRED JAN 2013.